/**@type {{
 * question: string,
 * answers: [ string, string ] | [ string, string, string] | [ string, string, string, string ]  | * 
 * correct:number
 * time:number
 * }[]}
 *  */
    export const questions = [
        {
            question: "Ancient Romans Boiled Vinegar And What To Make An Energy Drink??",
            answers: [
                'Goat Poop',
                'Cherries',
                'Lemon'
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "Who was the first person to sit down?",
            answers: [
                'Me',
                'Jim',
                'Lazlo'
            ],
            correct: 2,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "When did lelo and stich come out?",
            answers: [
                '1990',
                '2002',
                '2005'
            ],
            correct: 1,
            time: 20
    
    
        },
        {
            question: "Who were the first U.S cowboys",
            answers: [
                'Vaquors',
                'Minions',
                'Mexicans'
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
    {
        question: "How many super bowls have there been?",
        answers: [
            '50',
            '55',
            '45',
            '68',
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "What Is Scotland's National Animal??",
        answers: [
            'Horse',
            'Cat',
            'Unicorn',
            'Rock',
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
 {
        question: "A group of ravens is called?",
        answers: [
            'Flock',
            'Ching',
            'Unkindness',
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "Who was the 13th president?",
        answers: [
            'John Jay',
            'Millard Filmore',
            'Andrew Johnson'
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },
 {
        question: "Why Did Pirates Wear Earrings?",
        answers: [
            'Stomach Aches',
            'Eyesight',
            'For kicks'
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: " In Ancient Greece, Throwing An Apple At Someone Was A Declaration Of What??",
        answers: [
            'Love',
            'Despair',
            'Hate'
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "In North Carolina, It's Illegal To Do What??",
        answers: [
            'Steal',
            'Kill',
            'Sing out of tune'
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "When Do Babies Get Their Fingerprints??",
        answers: [
            '1 yr',
            '21 weeks',
            '6 months',
            '3 days'        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "What Bird Has Eyes That Are Bigger Than Its Brain?",
        answers: [
            'Robin',
            'Ostrich',
            'Penguin'
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "What Reptile Can't Stick Its Tongue Out???",
        answers: [
            'Lizards',
            'Crocs',
            'Snakes'
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },

 {
        question: "In The U.S.A., Every 12 Seconds Someone Does What In A Holiday Inn??",
        answers: [
            'Steal a towel',
            'Check out',
            'Swim'
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
 
    {
        question: " In Florida, It's Illegal For Unmarried Women To Do What On Sundays??",
        answers: [
            'Skydive',
            'Do Laundry',
            'Go on dates',
            'Clean',
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
  
    {
        question: "What do americans do 22 times a day?",
        answers: [
            'Yawn',
            'Sneeze',
            'Open the fridge',
            'Cry',
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    ]
    
    
    
    
    
    

    
    
    
    
    
   
    
    
    
    
    
